http://www.surgcare.co.za/index.php/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy | Dr Matley & Partners
+27 82 222 1666 (24h Emergency Call)
Practice ProfilePioneersTeamProcedures
Arterial SurgeryBreast SurgeryColorectal & Upper GI SurgeryEndoscopic SurgeryHepatobiliary / Pancreatic SurgeryLaparoscopic SurgeryOther SurgeryVenous SurgerySurgeons
Dr MatleyProf BaigrieDr OoditDr TunnicliffeDr NdhluniDr ForleeDr TheunissenDr LorimerDr HewatDr MareeDr NathaDr
HamptonDr DalwaiResources
Schedule AppointmentInfo SheetsBowel PrepNewslettersNews
Medical 10 Results (2019)Medical 10 Photos (2019)Contact
Home
About
Practice ProfilePioneersTeamProcedures
Arterial SurgeryBreast SurgeryColorectal & Upper GI SurgeryEndoscopic SurgeryHepatobiliary / Pancreatic SurgeryLaparoscopic SurgeryOther SurgeryVenous SurgerySurgeons
Dr MatleyProf BaigrieDr OoditDr TunnicliffeDr NdhluniDr ForleeDr TheunissenDr LorimerDr HewatDr MareeDr NathaDr
HamptonDr DalwaiResources
Schedule AppointmentInfo SheetsBowel PrepNewslettersNews
Medical 10 Results (2019)Medical 10 Photos (2019)Contact
Home
About
Practice ProfilePioneersTeamProcedures
Arterial SurgeryBreast SurgeryColorectal & Upper GI SurgeryEndoscopic SurgeryHepatobiliary / Pancreatic SurgeryLaparoscopic SurgeryOther SurgeryVenous SurgerySurgeons
Dr MatleyProf BaigrieDr OoditDr TunnicliffeDr NdhluniDr ForleeDr TheunissenDr LorimerDr HewatDr MareeDr NathaDr
HamptonDr DalwaiResources
Schedule AppointmentInfo SheetsBowel PrepNewslettersNews
Medical 10 Results (2019)Medical 10 Photos (2019)Contact
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
sosmpress
2017-11-22T13:39:46+00:00
Content of patient informationWe will ensure that:
patient information shall be obtained only for the purpose of delivering and improving the Services and will not be processed in any manner incompatible with this purpose;
patient information shall be adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the abovementioned purpose for which it is collated and/or processed;
patient information shall be accurate, and where necessary, kept up to date and reasonable steps shall be taken to ensure that information which is inaccurate and/or incomplete, having regard to the purpose for which it was collected, is erased or rectified;
patient information shall be kept in a format which permits identification for no longer than is necessary for the purpose for which the information was collected or processed.
Access to patient informationWe will ensure that:
access to, or disclosure of patient information will not be authorized without the documented commitment of the intended recipient so as to maintain confidentiality and the rightful use of such information;
access to patient information by our personnel, contract workers, consultants, service providers or suppliers will be restricted to the level of access needed to effectively perform delegated or contracted duties and/or the level of service needed to render a reliable and effective service to our patients.
Preventative measuresWe will ensure that appropriate technical and organisational measures shall be taken against the unauthorised access, processing or disclosure of patient information.
HomePrivacy PolicyDisclaimerPayment PolicyUseful LinksContact
CONTACT INFO
+27 21 797 1755 (o/h)
+27 82 222 1666 (24h emergency)
surgeons@surgcare.co.za
© Dr Matley & Partners | All Rights Reserved
